Henry A. Kissinger Papers, Part III: Guide to the Yale University Library Collection
Manuscripts and Archives
- Telephone Conversation Transcript Copies, 1969 - 1974; Series IV
  - Transcripts, 1974 July 19 (Box 197, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1974 July 20-21 (Box 197, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1974 July 22-25 (Box 197, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1974 July 26-31 (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1974 August 1-8 (Box 198, Folder 2)
- Writing and Research Materials, 1950 - 2006; Series V
  The writings and research materials document Kissinger’s work as an author and commentator on foreign policy and international affairs after he left government service in 1977. The majority of materials are research files and most of those concern three books, the first and third volumes of his memoirs, White House Years (1977) and Years of Renewal (1999), and his history of international relations and statecraft Diplomacy (1994). The research files are comprised primarily of copies of telephone conversation transcripts, government records, and publications, often collated by topic and annotated by his research assistants and occasionally by Kissinger himself. There is little other drafting material like notes or outlines and no book or chapter drafts in these files. There is a separate section of files concerning a proposed PBS television series on diplomacy based on lectures he gave at Georgetown University in 1980 which was apparently never produced.
  Writings in this series consist of Kissinger’s syndicated articles and a photocopy of the final submitted version of his Harvard University undergraduate thesis, “The Meaning of History.” The articles on international affairs from 1984 to 2006 were syndicated by the Los Angeles Times Syndicate and usually appeared in the Washington Post, Los Angeles Times, and New York Post. The article files usually contain handwritten drafts and the published versions of the articles.
  Series V is arranged into four subseries: PBS television series on diplomacy, Research files for books, Syndicated articles, and Undergraduate thesis.
  - PBS television series on diplomacy
    - General, 1964 - 1982 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Georgetown University lectures, 1980 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - "HK Philosophy of Foreign Policy" by Peter W. Rodman, 1977 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Hoyt, Austin-correspondence, 1986 - 1987 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Material for Michael Korda meeting [1 of 2], 1980, undated (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Material for Michael Korda meeting [2 of 2], 1980, undated (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Program outlines [1 of 12], 1980 - 1987 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Program outlines [2 of 12], 1980 - 1987 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - Program outlines [3 of 12], 1980 - 1987 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Program outlines [4 of 12], 1980 - 1987 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Program outlines [5 of 12], 1980 - 1987 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Program outlines [6 of 12], 1980 - 1987 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Program outlines [7 of 12], 1980 - 1987 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Program outlines [8 of 12], 1980 - 1987 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Program outlines [9 of 12], 1980 - 1987 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Program outlines [10 of 12], 1980 - 1987 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Program outlines [11 of 12], 1980 - 1987 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Program outlines [12 of 12], 1980 - 1987 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - WGBH and meeting with Austin Hoyt, Jan 5, 1987, 1982 - 1986 (Box 200, Folder 10)
  - Research files for books
    - Diplomacy
      - America's role in the world, 1990 - 1992 (Box 201, Folder 1)
      - Korea-Harry Truman, 1951-1957, undated (Box 201, Folder 2)
      - Liberals on detente (1974) [1 of 2], 1985 (Box 201, Folder 3)
      - Liberals on detente (1974) [2 of 2], 1985 (Box 201, Folder 4)
      - United States-Soviet relations (pre-Nixon) [1 of 4], 1956 - 1992 (Box 201, Folder 5)
      - United States-Soviet relations (pre-Nixon) [2 of 4], 1956 - 1992 (Box 201, Folder 6)
      - United States-Soviet relations (pre-Nixon) [3 of 4], 1956 - 1992 (Box 201, Folder 7)
      - United States-Soviet relations (pre-Nixon) [4 of 4], 1956 - 1992 (Box 202, Folder 1)
      - Vietnam-John Kerry 1992 POW/MIA hearings [1 of 2], 1971 - 1975 (Box 202, Folder 2)
      - Vietnam-John Kerry 1992 POW/MIA hearings [2 of 2], 1971-1975, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 3)
      - Vietnam-Nixon years [1 of 2], 1969 - 1975; 1992 (Box 202, Folder 4)
      - Vietnam-Nixon years [2 of 2], 1969 - 1975; 1992 (Box 202, Folder 5)
      - Vietnam War-United States history [1 of 3], 1954 - 1990 (Box 202, Folder 6)
      - Vietnam War-United States history [2 of 3], 1954 - 1990 (Box 202, Folder 7)
      - Vietnam War-United States history [3 of 3], 1954 - 1990 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - White House Years
      - China, 1969, 1969 - 1978 (Box 203, Folder 1)
      - China, 1970, 1970 - 1971 (Box 203, Folder 2)
      - China, 1971, 1971, undated (Box 203, Folder 3)
      - China, 1972, 1971 - 1972 (Box 203, Folder 4)
      - Chronology, 1969 [1 of 2], Circa 1969-circa 1977 (Box 203, Folder 5)
      - Chronology, 1969 [2 of 2], Circa 1969-circa 1977 (Box 203, Folder 6)
      - Chronology, 1970 [1 of 3], Circa 1970-circa 1977 (Box 203, Folder 7)
      - Chronology, 1970 [2 of 3], Circa 1970-circa 1977 (Box 203, Folder 8)
      - Chronology, 1970 [3 of 3], Circa 1970-circa 1977 (Box 203, Folder 9)
      - Chronology, Jan-Jun 1971 [1 of 3], Circa 1971-circa 1977 (Box 203, Folder 10)
      - Chronology, Jan-Jun 1971 [2 of 3], Circa 1971-circa 1977 (Box 204, Folder 1)
      - Chronology, Jan-Jun 1971 [3 of 3], Circa 1971-circa 1977 (Box 204, Folder 2)
      - Chronology, Jul-Dec 1971 [1 of 3], Circa 1971-circa 1977 (Box 204, Folder 3)
      - Chronology, Jul-Dec 1971 [2 of 3], Circa 1971-circa 1977 (Box 204, Folder 4)
      - Chronology, Jul-Dec 1971 [3 of 3], Circa 1971-circa 1977 (Box 204, Folder 5)
      - Chronology-China draft, 1971, Circa 1971-circa 1977 (Box 204, Folder 6)
      - Chronology-presidential items only, 1969-1971 [1 of 2], Circa 1969-circa 1977 (Box 204, Folder 7)
      - Chronology-presidential items only, 1969-1971 [2 of 2], Circa 1969-circa 1977 (Box 204, Folder 8)
      - Chronology-presidential items only, 1970 [1 of 2], Circa 1970-circa 1977 (Box 205, Folder 1)
      - Chronology-presidential items only, 1970 [2 of 2], Circa 1970-circa 1977 (Box 205, Folder 2)
      - Conversations with North Vietnamese-list, 1969 - 1973 (Box 205, Folder 3)
      - Defense, 1970-1972 [1 of 3], 1970 - 1971 (Box 205, Folder 4)
      - Defense, 1970-1972 [2 of 3], 1970 - 1971 (Box 205, Folder 5)
      - Defense, 1970-1972 [3 of 3], 1970 - 1971 (Box 205, Folder 6)
      - Edits to add to White House Years, 1968 - 1987 (Box 205, Folder 7)
      - "Kissinger philosophy of foreign policy", 1977 - 1978 (Box 205, Folder 8)
      - Kissinger press conference extracts, 1972 (Box 205, Folder 9)
      - "Kissinger views on Vietnam, 1969-1970", 1977 (Box 206, Folder 1)
      - Maps and photographs for White House Years, 1970-1979, undated (Box 206, Folder 2)
      - Maps of Indochina, 1970, undated (Box 206, Folder 3)
      - Maps of Middle East, 1967 - 1973 (Box 206, Folder 4)
      - Public statements of the president on SALT, 1969 - 1971 (Box 206, Folder 5)
      - SALT and defense, 1972, 1971 - 1972 (Box 206, Folder 6)
      - SALT public pressures, 1970 (Box 206, Folder 7)
      - "The Setting," 1968, 1965 - 1969 (Box 206, Folder 8)
      - Transition, 1968 - 1969 (Box 206, Folder 9)
      - Transition, 1968-1969, 1977 (Box 206, Folder 10)
      - Troop withdrawal from Vietnam-public statements by Richard Nixon and Kissinger [1 of 2], 1969 - 1970 (Box 207, Folder 1)
      - Troop withdrawal from Vietnam-public statements by Richard Nixon and Kissinger [2 of 2], 1969 - 1970 (Box 207, Folder 2)
      - United States-Soviet relations, Circa 1968-circa 1971 (Box 207, Folder 3)
      - United States-Soviet relations-public and congressional pressures, 1971 [1 of 3], 1970 - 1971 (Box 207, Folder 4)
      - United States-Soviet relations-public and congressional pressures, 1971 [2 of 3], 1970 - 1971 (Box 207, Folder 5)
      - United States-Soviet relations-public and congressional pressures, 1971 [3 of 3], 1970 - 1971 (Box 207, Folder 6)
      - United States-Soviet relations-public criticism, 1969, 1968 - 1969 (Box 207, Folder 7)
      - Vietnam, 1969, 1968 - 1969 (Box 208, Folder 1)
      - Vietnam, 1969 [1 of 2], 1969 - 1972 (Box 208, Folder 2)
      - Vietnam, 1969 [2 of 2], 1969 - 1972 (Box 208, Folder 3)
      - Vietnam, 1970, 1970-1971, undated (Box 208, Folder 4)
      - Vietnam, 1972, 1972 - 1973 (Box 208, Folder 5)
      - Vietnam agreement, Jan 1973 (Box 208, Folder 6)
      - Vietnam agreement-copy of initialed texts, 1973 (Box 208, Folder 7)
      - Vietnam casualties and troop withdrawals, 1972-1977, undated (Box 208, Folder 8)
      - Vietnam critics, 1969 (Box 208, Folder 9)
      - Vietnam dissent, 1970 (Box 208, Folder 10)
      - Vietnam-public pressures, Jul-Dec 1970 [1 of 2] (Box 208, Folder 11)
      - Vietnam-public pressures, Jul-Dec 1970 [2 of 2] (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Years of Renewal
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-detente, 1974; 1985 - 1996 (Box 209, Folder 2)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-detente and Soviet Union, 1974, 1992-1996, undated (Box 209, Folder 3)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-Eastern Europe visits before and after Helsinki, 1975 - 1979 (Box 209, Folder 4)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-Gerald R. Ford and Middle East diplomacy, 1974-1977, undated (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-Helsinki, 1975 (Box 209, Folder 6)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-Helsinki and Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn, 1975, 1998, undated (Box 209, Folder 7)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-Helsinki and Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn, additional [1 of 2], 1975 - 1998 (Box 209, Folder 8)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-Helsinki and Aleksandr Solzhenitsyn, additional [2 of 2], 1975 - 1998 (Box 209, Folder 9)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-intelligence investigations, 1974-1979, 1995-1996, undated (Box 209, Folder 10)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-Mayaguez, 1975-1979, 1995-1996, undated (Box 209, Folder 11)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-Middle East, 1973-1979, 1996, undated (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-Middle East shuttle diplomacy, 1975-1979, 1996, undated (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-Southeast Asia, 1975-1979, undated (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-Soviet Union and China, 1974-1996, undated (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-transition of Gerald R. Ford to presidency and Cyprus [1 of 2], 1969-1980, 1994-1996, undated (Box 210, Folder 5)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-transition of Gerald R. Ford to presidency and Cyprus [2 of 2], 1969-1980, 1994-1996, undated (Box 210, Folder 6)
      - Anecdotal "color" papers-United States and Soviet bombers, 1991 - 1996 (Box 210, Folder 7)
      - Angola-congressional and public pressures, 1975-1976 [1 of 2], 1994 (Box 210, Folder 8)
      - Angola-congressional and public pressures, 1975-1976 [2 of 2], 1994 (Box 211, Folder 1)
      - Angola-miscellaneous public and congressional opinion, 1969 - 1980 (Box 211, Folder 2)
      - Backnotes, 1967 - 1981 (Box 211, Folder 3)
      - Declassified telephone conversation transcripts-redacted copies, Nov 1974-Apr 1975 [1 of 2], 1974 - 1975 (Box 211, Folder 4)
      - Declassified telephone conversation transcripts-redacted copies, Nov 1974-Apr 1975 [2 of 2], 1974 - 1975 (Box 211, Folder 5)
      - Domestic environment-detente and Middle East, Aug-Dec 1974 [1 of 3], 1974 - 1996 (Box 211, Folder 6)
      - Domestic environment-detente and Middle East, Aug-Dec 1974 [2 of 3], 1974 - 1996 (Box 211, Folder 7)
      - Domestic environment-detente and Middle East, Aug-Dec 1974 [3 of 3], 1974 - 1996 (Box 211, Folder 8)
      - Domestic environment-intelligence community, Aug-Dec 1974, 1974 - 1976; 1996 (Box 211, Folder 9)
      - Editorial correspondence, 1980-1981, undated (Box 212, Folder 1)
      - Edits to add to Years of Upheaval, 1973-1981, undated (Box 212, Folder 2)
      - Halloween massacre, 1975; 1997 (Box 212, Folder 3)
      - Halloween massacre-updated, 1975; 1977 (Box 212, Folder 4)
      - Lebanon-civil war, 1975-1976 [1 of 2], 1975 - 1995 (Box 212, Folder 5)
      - Lebanon-civil war, 1975-1976 [2 of 2], 1975 - 1995 (Box 212, Folder 6)
      - Liberals on detente [1 of 3], 1974 - 1992 (Box 212, Folder 7)
      - Liberals on detente [2 of 3], 1974 - 1992 (Box 212, Folder 8)
      - Liberals on detente [3 of 3], 1974 - 1992 (Box 213, Folder 1)
      - List of Kissinger speeches, 1973 - 1977 (Box 213, Folder 2)
      - Maps for Years of Upheaval [1 of 2], 1973-1982, undated (Box 213, Folder 3)
      - Maps for Years of Upheaval [2 of 2], 1973-1982, undated (Box 213, Folder 4)
      - Middle East shuttle diplomacy anecdotes, 1980, undated (Box 213, Folder 5)
      - Namibia, 1997 (Box 213, Folder 6)
      - Photographs for Years of Upheaval, 1981-1982, undated (Box 213, Folder 7)
      - SALT, Circa 1994 (Box 213, Folder 8)
      - Vietnam, 1975, 1973 - 1975 (Box 213, Folder 9)
      - Zimbabwe statement, 1982 (Box 213, Folder 10)
  - Syndicated articles
    - "Facing Reality in the World Debt Crisis," Los Angeles Times, Jun 24, 1984 (Box 213, Folder 11)
    - "Should We Try to Defend against Russia's Missiles?," Washington Post, Jul 23, 1984 (Box 213, Folder 12)
    - "Peace Is Not the Only Objective," Washington Post, Jul 29, 1984 (Box 213, Folder 13)
    - "U.S. Must Lead in Free Trade," Los Angeles Times, Oct 22, 1984 (Box 213, Folder 14)
    - "Reagan Must Seize the Middle Ground," Los Angeles Times, Nov 18, 1984 (Box 213, Folder 15)
    - "How Will We Measure Progress?," Washington Post, Dec 16, 1984 (Box 213, Folder 16)
    - "Pressure Points in the Gulf," Washington Post, Feb 5, 1985 (Box 213, Folder 17)
    - "Cutting Defense: The Wrong Idea," Washington Post, Mar 5, 1985 (Box 213, Folder 18)
    - "A Tragedy of War in Four Acts," Los Angeles Times, Apr 7, 1985 (Box 213, Folder 19)
    - "Charting a Course to the Summit," Los Angeles Times, May 5, 1985 (Box 213, Folder 20)
    - "Building a Bridge of Hope to Our Latin Neighbors," Washington Post, Jun 25, 1985 (Box 213, Folder 21)
    - "Leaping (So Soon) into the Middle East," Washington Post, Jul 11, 1985 (Box 213, Folder 22)
    - "Talking down Arms," Los Angeles Times, Sep 8, 1985 (Box 213, Folder 23)
    - "U.S. Frictions, Japan Factions," Los Angeles Times, Oct 6, 1985 (Box 213, Folder 24)
    - "Just an Episode, or a Historical Breakthrough?," Los Angeles Times, Nov 17, 1985 (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - "Past Policy, Future Pressure," Los Angeles Times, Dec 15, 1985 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - "China Tries World's Newest Economic Model," Los Angeles Times, Jan 19, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - "What Next When U.S. Intervenes?," Los Angeles Times, Mar 9, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - "First, 'Latinize' It," Washington Post, Apr 13, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - "Redo NATO to Restore the Alliance," Los Angeles Times, May 11, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - "Soccer Imitates Life," Washington Post, Jun 29, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - "Defining Defense by U.S. Purpose," Los Angeles Times, Jul 27, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - "South Africa: A Policy to Share Power," Los Angeles Times, Sep 7, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - "Reagan Was Right to Shun 'Accords' That Were Traps," Los Angeles Times, Oct 19, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - "A Formula from Reykjavik: Arms Proposals Full of Peril," Los Angeles Times, Nov 16, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - "Not Its Power, but Its Weakness," Washington Post, Dec 21, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - "Next U.S. Policy for the Pacific," Los Angeles Times, Jan 25, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 13)
    - "Faulting U.S. Posture for Negotiations with Soviets," Los Angeles Times, Mar 8, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 14)
    - "Forget the 'Zero Option'," Washington Post, Apr 5, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 15)
    - "An Arms Agreement—On Two Conditions," by Richard Nixon and Kissinger, Washington Post, Apr 26, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 16)
    - "Every Day, Deeper in Debt," Washington Post, May 24, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 17)
    - "Wandering in the Gulf," Washington Post, Jun 21, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 18)
    - "America's Contra Muddle," Washington Post, Jul 26, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 19)
    - "Real Bipartisanship on Central America," Washington Post, Sep 6, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 20)
    - "China Now Changing Rules and Ruling Party," Washington Post, Oct 25, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 21)
    - "Dealing from Reality," Los Angeles Times, Nov 22, 1987 (Box 214, Folder 22)
    - "Gorbachev Greets an Antagonist," Los Angeles Times, Jan 17, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 23)
    - "Mideast: To Find a Formula," Los Angeles Times, Feb 14, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 24)
    - "What a Mideast Peace Could Look Like," Washington Post, Feb 21, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 25)
    - "Preparing a New U.S. Position to Meet the Next World Order," Los Angeles Times, Mar 27, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 26)
    - "START: A Dangerous Rush for Agreement," Washington Post, Apr 24, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 27)
    - "Arab-Israel Grounds for a Settlement," Los Angeles Times, May 15, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 28)
    - "Reagan's Final Challenge," Washington Post, Jun 12, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 29)
    - "The Rise of Mexico," Washington Post, Aug 17, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 30)
    - "As the Kremlin Shakes, the West Must Be Wary," Los Angeles Times, Oct 16, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 31)
    - "The Challenge of a 'European Home'," Washington Post, Dec 4, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 32)
    - "Gorbachev and the West's Wishful Thinkers," Washington Post, Dec 20, 1988 (Box 214, Folder 33)
    - "First a Breakthrough with Mexico," Washington Post, Jan 11, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 34)
    - "Dealing with Moscow: A New Balance," Washington Post, Feb 7, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 35)
    - "Across the Gulf of Intransigence," Los Angeles Times, Mar 19, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 36)
    - "Reversing Yalta," Washington Post, Apr 16, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 37)
    - "The Drama in Beijing," Washington Post, Jun 11, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 38)
    - "The Caricature of Deng as a Tyrant Is Unfair," Washington Post, Aug 1, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 39)
    - "War Roared into Vacuum Formed by a Sidestepping of Statesmanship," Los Angeles Times, Aug 27, 1989 (Box 214, Folder 40)
    - "Europe Returns to Center Stage as the Fulcrum for World Tension," Los Angeles Times, Oct 8, 1989 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - "Finding a New U.S. Policy to Fit a New World of Opportunity," Los Angeles Times, Nov 5, 1989 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - "Old Fears and the New Germany," Washington Post, Jan 14, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - "Drawing Fine Political Lines for Europe's Future," Los Angeles Times, Feb 4, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - "New World Acoming—And a New Peril, Too," Los Angeles Times, Mar 4, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - "Germany, Neutrality and the 'Security System' Trap," Washington Post, Apr 15, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - "U.S. Strategy in a New World," New York Post, May 29, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - "Nations Can't Change Colors," by Anthony Day and Kissinger, Los Angeles Times, Jun 10, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - "Dull Defenses Dim Cup Play," by Anthony Day and Kissinger, Los Angeles Times, Jun 24, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - "Second Round Has Intensity, Mixed Results," by Anthony Day and Kissinger, Los Angeles Times, Jul 1, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - "West Germany Carries a Historic Burden," by Anthony Day and Kissinger, Los Angeles Times, Jul 8, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 11)
    - "Defensive Accordion Plays Off-key in World Cup Final Match," by Anthony Day and Kissinger, Los Angeles Times, Jul 15, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 12)
    - "The End of NATO?," Washington Post, Jul 24, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 13)
    - "The Game Has Just Begun," Washington Post, Aug 19, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 14)
    - "Decision Time in the Gulf," New York Post, Sep 25, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 15)
    - "U.S. Must Avoid Stalemate," New York Post, Nov 6, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 16)
    - "Thatcher Still Leads the Way," Washington Post, Dec 2, 1990 (Box 215, Folder 17)
    - "No Illusions about the USSR," Washington Post, Jan 22, 1991 (Box 215, Folder 18)
    - "False Dreams of a New World Order," Washington Post, Feb 26, 1991 (Box 215, Folder 19)
    - "The Soviet Union Searches for Its Own New Order," Los Angeles Times, Mar 31, 1991 (Box 215, Folder 20)
    - "Hard Choices to Make in the Gulf," Washington Post, May 5, 1991 (Box 215, Folder 21)
    - "Land for Time in the Middle East," Washington Post, Jun 2, 1991 (Box 215, Folder 22)
    - "No Time for a 'Grand Bargain'," Washington Post, Jul 9, 1991 (Box 215, Folder 23)
    - "Soviet Good Will—Don't Count on It," Washington Post, Aug 13, 1991 (Box 215, Folder 24)
    - "Russian Minefield," Washington Post, Sep 17, 1991 (Box 215, Folder 25)
    - "If Not Peace, at Least Progress," Washington Post, Oct 31, 1991 (Box 215, Folder 26)
    - "Redefining National Security," New York Post, Dec 3, 1991 (Box 215, Folder 27)
    - "Don't Resurrect an Empire," Washington Post, Jan 14, 1992 (Box 215, Folder 28)
    - "Europe Needs America," New York Post, Mar 3, 1992 (Box 215, Folder 29)
    - "Russian 'Democracy'? Not Yet," New York Post, Mar 31, 1992 (Box 215, Folder 30)
    - "Right in Our Own Backyard," New York Post, May 12, 1992 (Box 215, Folder 31)
    - "Charter of Confusion," Washington Post, Jul 5, 1992 (Box 215, Folder 32)
    - "The Path to Peaceful Coexistence in the Middle East," Washington Post, Aug 2, 1992 (Box 215, Folder 33)
    - "Let West Lift Bosnia Arms Ban," New York Post, Sep 22, 1992 (Box 215, Folder 34)
    - "A Tribute to Willy Brandt," New York Post, Oct 27, 1992 (Box 215, Folder 35)
    - "Somalia: Reservations," Washington Post, Dec 13, 1992 (Box 215, Folder 36)
    - "Clinton's Global Challenge," New York Post, Jan 26, 1993 (Box 215, Folder 37)
    - "U.S. Should Limit Bosnia Role," New York Post, Feb 23, 1993 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - "It's Russia That Counts, Not Yeltsin," New York Post, Mar 23, 1993 (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - "New Europe: Caught between Two Giants," New York Post, Apr 27, 1993 (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - "Bosnia: A Cease-Fire, but No Ground Troops," Washington Post, May 16, 1993 (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - "Why We Can't Withdraw from Asia," Washington Post, Jun 15, 1993 (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - "NAFTA: Clinton's Defining Task," Washington Post, Jun 20, 1993 (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - "A Recipe for Foreign Policy Chaos," New York Post, Sep 7, 1993 (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - "Defining a Rational Foreign Policy," New York Post, Oct 26, 1993 (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - "An Imprudent Plan for Reforming NATO," New York Post, Nov 16, 1993 (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - "Europe Needs a Strong NATO, Not Utopian Gimmicks," International Herald Tribune, Jan 24, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - "The Growing Irrelevance of U.S. Foreign Policy," New York Post, Mar 1, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 11)
    - "China: The Deadlock Can Be Broken," Washington Post, Mar 28, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 12)
    - "Mexico's Moment of Truth," Washington Post, Apr 5, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 13)
    - ''Courage in the Face of Wrenching Domestic Controversy'," Los Angeles Times Syndicate, Apr 27, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 14)
    - "South Africa: For Once, History Offers Hope," International Herald Tribune, May 16, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 15)
    - "The Right Decision on China," by Cyrus Vance and Kissinger, Washington Post, Jun 6, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 16)
    - "Goal Is to Gain Foothold Here," by Anthony Day and Kissinger, Los Angeles Times, Jun 19, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 17)
    - "Real Winners of Round One: Organizers," by Anthony Day and Kissinger, Los Angeles Times, Jul 3, 1994 (Box 216, Folder 18)